Excuse me, ma'am. Ma'am, question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I'm not a millionaire.
No?
No, I'm a billionaire.
You're a billionaire?
Yes.
How did you become a billionaire?
I run a tech company.
You run a tech company?
Yes.
How long have you been a business owner?
So I left Wall Street in 2013.
You were on Wall Street?
Yes. My job was to keep
rich people rich for a living.
So what was the most amount of
money that you made in a single year?
A billion dollars.
A lot.
Give me a range.
1.2 billion dollars.
1.2 billion?
Yes.
Are you a billionaire?
That makes me a billionaire, yes.
Have you ever met a billionaire?
Absolutely. I mean, the bank accounts are
billionaires and the homes are billionaires. Absolutely.
So where do the wealthiest people put their money?
I want you to think about
the richest people that you've ever met.
Okay, so here we go.
80% of their money, typically.
As a billionaire, what's the best financial
advice you would give to the younger generation?
If you want to start your own business.
Your last message to the younger generation
trying to become a billionaire in today's world.
I'm about to do something insane, guys.
I'm about to interview some of the richest
women in the entire world, including Sarah Blakely,
the youngest self-made female
billionaire in the entire world.
And I'm not kidding.
Right now, I'm standing in Beverly Hills, one
of the richest zip codes on the planet.
And I'm going to be going around to find some of the
richest women that live here to figure out how they built their fortunes.
But we're just getting started, you guys.
Because after this, I'm going to be flying across the country to Atlanta
to go meet and interview one of the richest female billionaires on Earth.
To figure out how she turned just $5,000 into a billion-dollar
empire, making her the youngest self-made female billionaire in the world.
So this video is about to
be insane for some of you.
It's going to be insane from start to finish.
So stay tuned until the end.
With that being said, let's go meet some billionaires.
Excuse me, ma'am. Ma'am.
Yes.
Question for you.
I'm going all over Beverly Hills
asking people, how did you get rich?
Worked hard.
What line of business are you in?
Film.
Producer, director? What are you doing?
Producer.
What was your most proud
accomplishment in the film industry?
Probably amassing almost $1 million.
I was $2 billion in revenue,
and now I got to go.
I'm so sorry.
Are you a business owner?
Real quick.
Can I show you my channel?
That way you can see it.
I'm so sorry.
You guys, I could not get the game from
her, but she said doing $2 billion in revenue.
That's just to put in perspective for you the kind of women, the kind of people
that are out here that we're going to be running into on these streets of Beverly Hills.
I wanted that one bad, but
we couldn't get it, you guys.
But I know that they're out here, and I am not going to
stop until I get a billion dollars worth of game for you all.
Come on.
Excuse me, ma'am.
How did you get rich?
How did I get rich?
Yes.
Working really, really hard.
And what line of business?
Are you a business owner?
Finance.
You were in finance on Wall Street or what?
That I can't tell you.
Wait.
So real quick.
I grew a channel to 17 million followers.
I've interviewed 25 billionaires in the last
four years, like Mark Cuban, Michael Rubin.
I asked successful people how they
made it for the younger generation.
So I wanted to ask you if there's one piece of financial advice that you
learned throughout your career that you could instill in the younger generation, what would that be?
Invest in things you understand.
Like what?
What was that for you?
What was the best vehicle?
Real estate.
And do you like residential or commercial?
What did you like?
Residential.
Why is that?
Because it's perfect for it.
And when did you buy real estate primarily?
This goes back to the 90s.
What's the best city to
buy real estate in today's world?
Oh, LA.
Anywhere where there's coastal properties.
A lot of people like red states.
Well, of course, because of politics.
So red states obviously are
better because of the tax breaks.
Did you ever own a business?
Yes.
What was the big issue you had?
A billion dollars.
A billion dollars?
Yes.
Are you serious?
Do you have anybody that doubted you in business?
No.
Nobody doubted you?
Why not?
Somebody that did cost them a lot of money.
So it's safe to say that it's
not a smart idea to bet against you?
Absolutely not a good idea.
Yeah.
Absolutely not.
Listen, all is fair, and I believe in
doing things fairly, and that business can be a
win-win for anybody.
But you should never get in a situation
where you think that somebody else is not worthy
of whatever.
Everybody deserves a break and a
chance to prove themselves in business.
What was the biggest challenge
that you faced running companies?
Because it's hard.
You have to-
Employees.
Why?
It was hard to get them?
Because employees, you have to hire people that you trust.
Men are always the best.
They're linear.
They're direct.
They're clear thinkers.
They're easy to take care of.
Women are emotional, difficult to do business with.
So did you hire a lot of-
That happens to be the truth.
So did you not hire
a lot of women employees then?
No.
Why not?
Are you serious?
Yes, I'm serious.
Even as a boss woman?
Yes.
You hire women that have men's instincts for business.
You mentioned buying real estate.
Yes.
Did you buy a lot of real estate?
You did?
Yes.
With each of your properties, did
you have an LLC for each property?
Yes.
How many LLCs do you own?
Over 50.
Over 50 LLCs?
How many was that?
Oh, it's critical.
I mean, here's the thing.
An LLC is a veil of
protection and everybody should understand their taxes.
It will serve you for the rest of your life.
For every business that I've started and
every property that I've acquired starting this
year, I've been using an LLC.
Super smart.
The company I used to start my
business and buy my properties was called Bizzy.
I started my LLC through them and it
was one of the smartest decisions because it protects
you.
I'm going to look at Bizzy.
You said you're 62 today.
Yes.
If me and you died tomorrow and you
had one more message for the younger generation, what
would that be?
Live while you're alive.
What's that mean?
Enjoy your life.
Guys, we just interviewed, I think,
a billionaire out here in Beverly Hills.
Did you hear what she said?
For every one of her businesses, for each
one of her real estate properties, she has
an LLC.
She's got not one, not
two, but 50 LLCs, you guys.
That is insane.
That should tell you something because
look, billionaires, they don't leave anything up
to chance.
They structure everything because the right
entity protects their personal assets, saves
them a ton of money on
taxes, and sets them up to scale.
That's exactly why I used
Bizzy when I was a kid.
I used Bizzy when I was starting out
and it helped me build a multi-million dollar business.
They make it insanely easy to start a business,
you guys, whether it's an LLC or an S-Corp.
You can literally get everything handled in
under 10 minutes and it's super affordable.
It is way cheaper and way easier than trying
to go hire a super expensive lawyer or an
accountant to set up your business.
So guys, trust me on this.
Stop what you're doing.
Be like the smart entrepreneurs.
Be like the rich entrepreneurs and use
Bizzy to set up your business today.
All you have to do is go down to
the link in the description of this video to start
your business through Bizzy today.
But with that being said,
let's get back to the video.
All right, you guys, so we're at our next
spot out here in Beverly Hills and a Maybach
just pulled up to the valet out here, so I'm
going to go up and see what they did to get
rich.
Let's go see who it is, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Ma'am.
Thank you.
Question for you.
Yes.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I'm not a millionaire.
No?
No, I'm a billionaire.
You're a billionaire?
Yes.
Are you actually?
How did you become a billionaire?
Well, working hard, shaping eyebrows.
So you're in the beauty business?
Yes, I'm in the beauty business.
I'm from the city of Beverly Hills.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
How long have you been a business owner?
Wow.
I started in 1997.
Are you self-made?
Yes, totally.
So you don't come from a lot of money?
No, I came here from a communist regime
from Romania, and I didn't speak the language.
I didn't have any money.
I didn't know anyone, and I really believed in eyebrows.
I go all over the world
interviewing billionaires to help the younger generation.
Can I get a minute with
you for the channel real quick?
Absolutely.
Did you take on a lot of investors?
No.
I mean, when I sold in 2018, I didn't have.
I own 100% of the company.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
How much did you sell for?
The company was evaluated of three billion.
Nobody believed in eyebrow business.
Did you have anybody that doubted you in business?
Oh, absolutely.
The landlord that I wanted to rent the space,
the bank didn't want to give me a credit card.
Everybody, my own husband didn't believe
that this will be a business.
Why didn't you listen to anybody else?
You know why?
Because I really believed it.
I really believed it.
Eyebrow is such an important feature in
our face, and I fix my own eyebrow.
This is how everything works.
I had pencil thin eyebrows in the eighties.
That was the fashion.
As a billionaire, what's the best financial
advice you would give to the younger generation?
If you want to start your
own business, watch the cash flow.
EBITDA is everything.
You know, that's-
It's all about the profit.
It's all about the profits.
Don't start spending money left and right.
When I started, I was driving a
beat up car that I spent $200.
And it didn't matter if my daughter thought
that I couldn't drive her to school because
the kids will make fun of her.
Or my clients, they didn't make fun.
But you know, the perception of people like,
oh, I have to fit in with everybody else.
I didn't care.
I had a bigger goals and it was important
for me to save every penny to put into my
business.
And for many years, this is what I did.
Every money I will generate, I
will put back into the business.
So you just kept reinvesting.
That's it.
Yes.
I didn't buy cars.
I worked nonstop.
So I didn't have even time
to spend the money I was making.
Now, when you started to generate cash flow and reinvest.
Yes.
You started to invest in the business.
How did you scale?
You have to scale to produce
more products, to widen the distribution.
And of course you start learning the business slowly.
You make a lot of mistakes.
I made many mistakes, but you learn from your mistakes.
And the key is to
never make the same mistake twice.
Social media right now, because
you asked me how I scale.
My daughter that worked with me and we
used to travel to promote the products in 2012,
she came to me and said, mom, maybe
we'll get into this app called Instagram and we
don't need to travel that much.
And I said, okay, let's try it.
Let's see.
Anybody else is like, ah, I don't believe it.
I don't want like absolutely anything.
I will try anything.
So we start posting pictures of
our products and it went viral.
And this is how we start sending products
to some makeup artists or women and men that
love products and our makeup.
And they used to do tutorial
on YouTube or pictures for Instagram.
And we're the first beauty brand.
We have a presence on Instagram
and this is how we scale.
It's exploded the company.
So social media changed the game for you.
Change completely the game.
So you always have to be alert.
Don't sit here and do the same
business that you did 20 years ago.
You have to adapt.
You got to pivot.
You have to pivot.
Business changes every day.
Right now with AI, I'm looking
into, I want to learn more.
I want to implement AI as much as
I can in finance, in product development, in distribution,
everything.
You've already built a billion dollar company.
You've became a billionaire.
Are you motivated to keep on going?
Oh, I work like I
can pay my rent next month.
So you're working like the rents do.
Oh yes.
Yes.
Like I love it.
I love what I do.
I don't even feel like I work.
And that's the key.
Actually, I find that I'm more successful
that I have a purpose every day.
Me and my daughter.
Money are great.
Don't get me wrong.
I love my whatever I have, what
I build, I work hard for it.
But that's not everything in life.
My family, my clients, my friends.
Every day I wake up.
I love challenge.
I love to solve problems.
I'm competitive.
So I have a great life.
Does money buy happiness?
Depends how you define happiness.
It buys freedom.
Freedom.
That's yes.
I think money buys freedom.
Not fulfillment though.
No fulfillment.
No, absolutely.
If me and you died tomorrow and you had
one more guiding principle to leave with the younger
generation, what would that be?
Oh my God.
Don't be afraid to start to
do whatever your heart is telling you.
Believe in yourself.
That's very important.
And you don't need to be like somebody else.
I know it's a lot of bullying right
now on social media at school for younger people.
You don't need to be like somebody else.
You don't.
It's okay.
I was skinny in school.
I was a gymnast.
I was the last one.
I was never like everybody else in the class.
But you know what?
I used to go to the library.
I used to read to do my homework
and be passionate about whatever I was doing.
And at the end of the day, you take
all that and you could build whatever you want.
You have amazing advice.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate you and wish you good
luck and everybody else that is watching.
Believe in yourself because you could do whatever you want.
I have to ask you, I
connect with all the billionaires I interview.
Can I get your contact?
Sure.
Guys, we just walked up to her.
What did she say?
I'm not a millionaire.
I'm a billionaire.
And she's a self-made one too.
Guys, she came from a communist country of
Romania, came here to Beverly Hills and built
a multi-billion dollar company, you guys.
She just gave a fantastic interview.
But the time has now come.
We're about to leave Beverly Hills and head
out to Atlanta, Georgia to go find the richest
woman that lived there.
We're going to meet up with the
youngest self-made female billionaire in the entire
world.
So head with us right now to
the airport to go fly out to Atlanta.
All right, you guys.
So we just got through security at the
Los Angeles airport and it is time now.
It's 11 o'clock at night and we're about to
fly out to Atlanta to go meet up with the
youngest self-made female billionaire of all time.
And we're going to figure out how she
built her billion dollar company and how you watching
can do the exact same thing.
And since Atlanta is home to more millionaires
and billionaires than most cities in the world,
we're going to go see who else we
can find in the richest areas in Atlanta.
So come with us right now to Atlanta, Georgia.
All right, you guys, it is 5am
and we just landed in Atlanta, Georgia.
And in just a few hours, I'm going to
be heading into the richest part of Atlanta and Buckhead
Village to go find some of the richest women that
live out here and see if we can get their
advice on how they built their wealth.
So stay tuned.
Let's head in and go see who we can find.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
Yes.
And how did you get rich?
I run a tech company.
You run a tech company?
Yes.
How long have you been a business owner?
So I left Wall Street in 2013.
You were on Wall Street?
Yes.
My job was to keep
rich people rich for a living.
I came up with the idea in 2013, but
we didn't make our money until 2017 as a business.
So what was the most amount of
money that you made in a single year?
Just shy of 10 million.
10 million dollars?
Yeah, just shy.
I go all over the world interviewing
the richest people to help the younger generation.
Can I get a minute with
you for our channel real quick?
Sure.
Have you ever met a billionaire?
Absolutely.
I mean, the bank accounts are
billionaires and the homes are billionaires.
Absolutely.
So where do the wealthiest people put their money?
I want you to think about
the richest people that you've ever met.
Where are they investing their money in today's world?
That's not talking about a lot.
Okay, so here we go.
80% of their money typically is in marketable securities.
So stocks, bonds, mutual funds, ETF, things like that.
10% of their wealth is in cash and
then the other 10% is in alternative investments.
Those are the investments that
you can't turn into cash quickly.
So things like real estate, things like
private investments that can give you the ability
to grow your wealth tremendously over
the next five to 10 years.
But it's all invested.
Wealthy people do not put their money in cash.
It's always in something that has
a potential to grow their wealth.
Do they keep their money in the savings account?
No.
Wealthy people put their money to work.
I think we all have job descriptions.
Even me running my business, they
give their money a job description.
You cannot save or work your way to wealth.
You can only invest your way there.
Did you come from a lot of money?
No, I did not come from a lot of money.
I came from a middle class household, two parents.
I was the first person in my family
to go to college, first entrepreneur, first millionaire
in my family.
You went to Howard?
I did.
I grew up right outside of DC.
Yes, I did.
The best HBCU in the world.
What was your turning point to financial freedom?
I think one of the biggest things I
learned about the 1% on Wall Street, they believe
they have power.
They believe they deserve to be in a room.
They believe they're supposed to be wealthy.
Most people don't even believe they
deserve a seat at the table.
Did you ever doubt yourself?
Absolutely.
I was the only black female
on my floor on Wall Street.
Sometimes I felt like I wasn't good enough, but
in that same moment, I knew that I could
be a billionaire because I was in that room.
Are you going to be a billionaire?
Absolutely.
Billion dollar CEO right here.
Yes.
Your last message to the younger generation?
Wealth does not have a color.
Therefore, it looks like you, it looks
like me, and it starts in the mind.
Just because you didn't grow up with wealth, just
because you may not have a lot of money
now.
It doesn't mean you can effectively
build wealth, but the key is ownership.
You have to create your wealth by owning companies
that you know you use and believe in or create
your own business.
You got amazing advice.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Thank you so much for your time.
I appreciate that.
I have to ask you, I connect
with all the millionaires that I interview.
Could I get your contact?
Absolutely.
Guys, she made $10 million in a single year.
She started off on Wall Street, left,
and built a multi-million dollar tech company,
you guys.
She just gave a phenomenal interview.
But my favorite part was when she broke
down what the richest people in the world, the
billionaires do with their money.
I just got to say, you guys,
you don't find this information in the news.
You don't find this information in school
or any of these online courses, you guys,
only here at the School of Hard Knocks.
But as you guys know, we got to keep
this one rolling because we got to keep going to
find the richest people in Atlanta, you guys.
Come on.
Arch, you guys, the time has now come.
We're going to be heading out to go
try and meet and interview the legendary, the youngest
self-made female billionaire in the entire world,
Sarah Blakely, at an event that's being
held about an hour south of Atlanta, Georgia, you guys.
We're going to show up and see if we can
actually get to her and interview her for our channel,
you guys.
Guys, I've interviewed like 25 plus billionaires.
But she would be one of the craziest
ones that I've ever done, being that she's one
of the only self-made woman billionaires, you guys.
So we're going to go do our best to try
and get this interview for you guys and go get
a million dollars worth of game.
Arch, you guys, so we just got to our destination.
We're going to be walking over right now
to go meet up with and interview the legend,
Sarah Blakely, to go figure
out how to become a billionaire.
Come on.
Hello.
How are you?
Hi.
Hi, Sarah.
How are you?
Good.
It's great to meet you.
Congratulations on this whole movement and success.
Yeah.
It's a great success that you've had.
Thank you so much.
Stopping people and asking them cool advice.
We appreciate that, yeah.
It's been a lot of fun.
We get to meet amazing people like you.
So it's all worth it, for sure.
Your story's been super inspiring to just learn
about and this is one I've been wanting
to do for a couple years now.
So I'm glad that we get to tell it
to our audience as well and you've had an amazing
journey.
So I know that they're looking forward to it.
My only request is that no holding back.
We're going to give them the secrets right now
on what it takes to build a billion dollar
brand.
Okay.
Can we do that?
Well, let's do it.
Perfect.
I got all the secrets.
I don't know.
What was your business?
I make butts look better.
My business was Spanx.
You're the founder of Spanx.
I'm the founder of Spanx.
What was the most amount of money
that you made in a single year?
A lot.
Give me a range.
Hundreds of millions.
Hundreds of millions of dollars?
Yeah.
And did you sell your company?
I did.
For how much?
I sold it for $1.2 billion.
You sold your company for $1.2 billion?
Yes.
Are you a billionaire?
That makes me a billionaire, yes.
For the ones that don't know, did you have
a lot of money when you started your business?
No.
I had $5,000 that I had saved
myself from selling fax machines door to door.
Okay.
For seven years.
Do you guys know what a fax is?
I sold them and I saved my money.
Was it easy to get
people to invest in your company?
It was so easy for me to get investors.
You know why?
I'm the only investor.
You never took on investors?
I never had a single
investor in Spanx other than me.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
I self-funded the entire 21 years.
Are you serious?
I'm serious.
So it was really easy to get an investor.
I sat down with myself and I was like, do
you want to spend your five grand on a vacation
or do you want to try to bet on yourself?
And you bet on yourself.
And I bet on myself.
So you don't think people should look to
give their company away and give that ownership
away to other people?
Listen, whatever you give away in your business,
you have to be very willing to give up.
You give up control.
You got to control.
You got to make all the shots.
Yeah.
I mean, I literally had no investors.
I got to answer to my own intuition,
which I really honored throughout the whole journey.
I always pay attention to intuition over
data and I don't think investors really understand
that.
So that worked in my favor
because intuition's not on a spreadsheet.
Did you face a lot of rejection?
Did I face a lot of rejection?
I sold fax machines for seven years door to door.
Rejection is my middle name.
I actually got rejected.
I was rejected so much.
People would rip up my business card in my
face and they would escort me out of buildings.
So by the time I started Spanx, rejection I
knew was just part of the formula to success.
Totally unfazed by rejection.
In fact, the more I would get rejected,
I'm like, oh, I'm closer to my yes.
What was the craziest thing that you did
as a business owner when you were starting out?
Oh my God, where do I start?
Well, definitely when I landed Neiman Marcus,
which was such a prestigious retailer, I got
a chance to be in one pocket
in the store of the whole hosiery department.
You know, Spanx was between like Donna Karan and Calvin.
And all these huge brands and
no one had heard of Spanx.
So I took bins that I bought at Office
Depot and stuck them at every cash register in the
store, which is so not okay.
Neiman Marcus has a very strict visual
apartment, but everybody thought somebody else approved
it.
So I was trying to get the product out
of the sleepiest corner of the store and move
it around to where the customers actually were.
So you have to do whatever
it takes to really become successful.
Absolutely.
You do whatever it takes.
And I always say, ask for forgiveness, not permission.
I love that.
I was like crazy.
And by the time they figured out no one
had approved that I could do that, the CEO of
Neiman said, whatever this girl is
doing, let her keep doing it.
So it's safe to say that nobody's gonna
run your business like you are, the business owner.
Yes.
I saw in a video that you did recently
that you think people should wait to talk about
their idea with other people, but there's
other people that maybe argue that and say
that you need to talk about your business and
run it by as many people as possible to
get your thoughts.
You disagree with that.
I disagree with that.
I waited a year before I told any friends
or family what I was working on, and that's
because I didn't want ego to
have to get involved too early.
Yeah.
early when ego gets involved you end up
spending your time defending it and explaining it instead
of pursuing it so i wanted to invest enough of
my personal time in creating this crazy idea that i
had i worked at night and on the weekends on it
until i knew i wouldn't turn back when i got doubt
and out of love your loved ones will bring up
things like my family was like sarah if it's such
a good idea why hasn't anybody already done it you know
even if this is a good idea the big guys will
knock you off in six months and you've spent your
life savings on it had i heard those things the
moment that i had the idea i would probably
still be selling fax machines or something else because
faxes aren't really around anymore but it's very
true because ideas are the most vulnerable in the
moment you have them and it's also people's
instinct to share the idea in the most vulnerable
stage because you get an idea and you turn
to your co-worker your husband your wife and you say
hey i've got an idea and out of love they'll
give you a list of like hey maybe you should consider
this and i didn't want that to happen so
intuitively i waited a year before i sat my
family down and then i got a job and i was like
i'm gonna do this and i'm gonna do that and i'm gonna
do this and i'm gonna do that and i'm gonna do
that and i'm gonna do that and they all thought i was
crazy they're like wait what this is the idea
you've been working on this new type of undergarment
i'm like yes it's gonna change the way women
around the world get dressed what did you see
differently than your family the people that were calling
you crazy the way that i saw that it
solved my problem with my clothes so all
undergarments prior to that were too thick they
were heavy they were made with thick material
and you could see the underwear you could see
panty lines i know you've had this problem but
anyway you could see panty lines and i wanted
a smooth look and so i thought of pantyhose and
i wanted to see pantyhose and i wanted to see pantyhose
only because it's like second skin the material
is so lightweight that if i could create an
undergarment out of that material it would
be breathable it wouldn't feel bulky it wouldn't
feel constricting in the way that other traditional
undergarments and girdles had so it really created
this whole new canvas for women and i want to
mention that i went into an industry that was in
a double digit decline and i find that fascinating a
lot of people like to chase trend and where is
everybody moving and i'm interested in like what industries
are sort of dying on the vine and why
and it's a lot of work and time and i want
to name a couple three things that i think are important
two first is that i'm not the only woman who's in
this industry my second thing is i'm not the only woman
who's in this industry and i'm not the only woman who's
in this industry i'm not the only woman who's in this industry
And hosiery was dying on the vine because fashion had changed,
women's styles had changed, and no one was solving the problem.
So when I created Spanx, I created a new type of undergarment that didn't exist
with the lightest weight material that was second skin in hosiery to go under women's clothes.
And bam, it was like lightning in a bottle, and I
filled a void that women had been waiting for me to fill.
Your last message to the younger generation
trying to become a billionaire in today's world.
Solve a problem, bet on yourself, and have fun.
Guys, I need you to stop what you're doing right now and like and
subscribe to this channel for tons of incredible content I've got coming very, very soon.
Because nobody is interviewing these kind of people.
Nobody's making content like this.
Guys, I'm 23, and I've interviewed over 25 billionaires.
And I've got more coming to you every single week.
The craziest, the most amazing
business owners in the entire world.
And I need you to do yourself a favor.
I want you to go down and click the link in the description of this video
to become a member of the number one most powerful community for entrepreneurs in the entire world.
The School of Mentors.
And inside of this community, you get direct access to the multimillionaires
and the billionaires that I interview on this channel every single week.
Where you get to ask your questions
directly to multimillionaires and billionaires just like Sarah.
Where they give you actionable advice on how to
build your first million dollar and maybe billion dollar business.
So I can't wait to see you on the inside.
Just go down to the link
in the description of this video.
With that being said, I'll
see you in the next video.